<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Extended Surgery (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ExtendedSurgery</packageId>
  <author>Kilroy232</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ExtendedSurgery</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Kilroy232s mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1312089354

- Replaced the vanilla overwrites with a patch instead

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ExtendedSurgery][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
This mod adds new basic surgeries intended for mid to late game play that will help keep colonists happier and also stay as close to the vanilla game as possible.

With the ability to add replace whole limbs with bionics I think it is only reasonable that a player can expect to have the ability to preform less complex but still important surgeries. This is the premise for this mod.

The mod includes prosthetics for missing ears, eyes and noses to prevent colonists from picking on disfigured people. The ability to replace any shattered bone and to heal scratches to help reduce the amount of pain a colonist is in and to improve their productivity.

I have added the ability to harvest and replace natural eyes

The mod doesn't require any research but you need to have a colonist with a high enough level of caring for all of the surgeries as well as artistics for the prostetics.

--You DO NOT need to start a new game for this mod--
--Note that bones are replaced with Plasteel so you must have some to preform the operation--

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2520284325][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/ExtendedSurgery?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
</ModMetaData>